https://www.exede.com/legal/

DISH TV
What Is Viasat?
Order Now
Buy today and get 3-month introductory pricing — save up to $150! Learn more
Buy today and get 3-month introductory pricing — up to 40% savings! Learn more
DISH TV
What Is Viasat?
Legal
CALL TODAY:
Viasat General Privacy Notice
This privacy notice describes the type of information Viasat collects from users who are not Viasat customers (such as those who access our websites), how we use and when we may disclose such information. Last updated: June 25, 2020
Details and Restrictions (residential and business)
This document describes our residential and business service plans. Last updated: November 19, 2020
Viasat Applicant Privacy Policy
This policy describes how we collect, store, process, transfer, share, and use data when you apply for a position with Viasat. Last updated: September 27, 2018
Viasat Internet subscribers
Policies applicable to all internet subscribers
Subscriber Privacy Policy
This policy describes the type of information Viasat collects, how we use it and when we may disclose it. Last updated: July 27, 2020
Network Management Policy
This policy describes how we manage Viasat’s network to provide all customers with a high-quality online experience. Last updated: January 15, 2019.
Acceptable Use Policy
This policy describes acceptable use of the Viasat, Exede and Wildblue Internet services as well as permissible and prohibited conduct when using the services.Last updated: November 30, 2017
Residential - Viasat Internet (formerly Exede Internet) services
Customer Agreement (residential)
This agreement applies to Viasat, Exede and WildBlue residential subscribers.
Last updated: June 4, 2020
Data Allowance Policy (residential)
This policy applies to the Classic, Evolution and Liberty plans. Last updated: June 4, 2020
Unlimited Data Policy
This policy applies to the unlimited data plans. Last updated: June 4, 2020
Bandwidth Usage Policy
This policy applies to the Freedom plans. Last updated: January 15, 2019
SMS Terms and Conditions
This document applies to your use of our text messaging option. Last updated: March 21, 2018
Viasat Mobile Application End User License Agreement
This agreement applies to your use of Viasat’s mobile application. Last updated: June 7, 2018
Viasat Mobile Application Privacy Notice
This agreement applies to your use of Viasat’s mobile application. Last updated: April 7, 2020
Viasat Shield Application End User Terms and Conditions
This agreement applies to your use of Viasat Shield application and service. Last updated: April 7, 2020
End User License Agreement for Email Services
This agreement applies to your use of our Exede or WildBlue email service. Last updated: November 30, 2017
Viasatretailer.com Privacy Notice
The policy applies to all users of viasatretailer.com (Managed Website Application). Last updated: January 30, 2018
Residential - WildBlue Internet service
Network Management Policy - WildBlue
This policy describes how we manage the WildBlue network to provide all customers with a high-quality online experience.
Last updated: November 30, 2017
Data Allowance Policy (Residential) - Wildblue
This policy applies to the WildBlue internet service plans. Last updated: November 30, 2017
Subscriber Privacy Policy - WildBlue
This policy describes the type of information Viasat collects, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. Last updated: July 27, 2020
Limited Warranty - WildBlue
This document applies only to customers who purchased their equipment from Viasat and explains Viasat’s limited warranty of the equipment.
Last updated: November 30, 2017
End User License Agreement for Email Services
This agreement applies to your use of our Exede or WildBlue email service. Last updated: November 30, 2017
Business Internet service
Customer Agreement (business)
This agreement applies to Viasat and Exede Business subscribers. Last updated: May 28, 2019
Data Allowance Policy (business)
This policy applies to the Viasat Business plans. Last updated: May 13, 2019
Viasat In-Flight Wi-Fi
Viasat In-Flight Wi-Fi Privacy Policy This policy describes the type of information Viasat collects, how we use it, and when we may disclose it when using our in-flight internet service.
Last updated: December 4, 2018
Viasat In-Flight Wi-Fi Acceptable Use Policy This policy outlines acceptable use of the in-flight internet service as well as permissible and prohibited conduct when using the in-flight internet service. Last updated: December 4, 2018
